Antoine Gauthier

Full Stack Developer

Email gantoin@pm.me



Tech

Java

Spring (Boot, Cloud, Security)

Microservices

Jenkins

SQL

Hibernate

Apache Kafka

JPA

Swagger

PL/SQL

Python

Git

Shell

Linux

JavaScript

AngularJS

ReactJS

ExtJS

HTML5

CSS3

SCSS

Languages

French - Fluent

English - B1

Ukrainian - C2

Hobbies

Bitcoir

Blockchain

Cryptocurrency

Traveling

Cycling

Mountains

Profile

I am a freelance developer with five years of professional experience. I am mainly experienced in back-end development (Java/Spring, SQL, PL/SQL, Apache Kafka) and can do front-end with React, Angular, or ExtJS. I am looking for challenging assignments in an exciting industry to implement my Java skills and improve my JavaScript skills.

Experiences

JAVA/SQL Developer

SAP Concur - Since January 2022

- Java development on a web application for travel management and allowances
- PL/SQL functions, procedures and scripts to update data in an Oracle database
- Ext JS and SCSS development for front-end rework

Back-end developer

DoubleTrade - July 2019 to January 2022

- Java 11, microservices architecture, Apache Kafka, Spring Cloud, Docker, continuous integration with GitLab Cl
- Scrum, code review/pair-programming, Pull/Merge requests
- Development of new APIs for a SaaS business intelligence application on public markets in France

Full Stack Developer

Wemoov - April 2019 to June 2019

 Development of a back-office and APIs for video editing with FFmpeg using JHipster with Java, AngularJS, SQL, Jenkins and Git

Web Developer

Department of Justice - January 2018 to August 2018

Redesign of internal applications for collecting data from the
administrations to produce statistics: Java, Angular, Docker, SQL, Git and SVN

Education

Professional degree in computer systems and software

Nantes (France) University (2016 - 2017)

Advanced Technician's Certificate

La Coliniere High school (2014 - 2016)

IT services for organizations option B software solutions and business applications